Hello there!
Look, it's him!
It's good to see you, Boxxo!
We'll get you to safety.
We landed on a boat that was adrift,
then floated on over to this here island.
We've been rescued, I think.
I'm tempted to put up my
barrier, but I shan't.
She's my partner, so
I'll take my medicine.
Stay strong and brace for impact.
Why'd you send me flying, Eddie?
I know you're excited to see Boxo, but
you've got to be more gentle with him.
Otherwise, he could get hurt.
Oh man, I'm real sorry.
I was just so excited.
I've got to turn that
frown upside-down stat.
I missed you, you big lug.
Oh boy, that smile's
gonna void my warranty.
Nice, that is a beautiful reunion gift.
You know, I was pretty worried too.
Don't I get a little something, huh?
It would be lame to give her
the same gift I gave my llamas.
I'll surprise and delight
with shock and awe.
Form, change, cancel machine!
Huh?
You're giving me a bunch of balls?
Oh, they're tiny toy tools.
How clever.
I've never seen some of these things
before, but they could come in handy.
I'll use them as a reference.
Hmm.
Pitti's here, too.
Don't you think I deserve a gift?
My fave clam likes sweet
treats and flowers.
Something sweet. Oh, snap! Eureka!
A parfait keychain.
Japan is undefeated in the world
of plastic food, tchotchkes.
This is incredible.
Thanks so much.
Mission successful! Wait. What?
Say, Boxo,
am I imagining things or have you and Pity
gotten a lot cozier since I last saw you?
Don't even try to deny it.
The two of you are definitely
too close for comfort.
Not gonna lie, she's a big Boxo fan
after all the time we spent together.
But it's innocent.
I'm like a big metal brother or
even just a beloved magic item.
Back me up, Pity!
Boxo and I are quite close.
We sleep together.
share our meals, and even
use the restroom together.
Aw, yeesh.
She's not wrong, but a little
tact would have gone a long way.
On the outside, I'm just a big metal box,
but inside, I've still got a human soul.
In this new world of wonders,
I travel to and fro on the back
of my super strong partner, Lamas.
The name's Boxo. Hello there.
That means yes, by the way.
I feel my burnt one.
I feel my grit.
I feel my grit. I feel my grit.
No, I want to know.
I feel my grit.
Eina Bernard.
Ultra. Your arrogant.
I'll see you from the end of the year.
Can't believe you in the future.
I hope you enjoyed it.
I want to recover!
If I know you will do
it... I will live him
up...
I know of a base on a small island behind
the Stratum Lord they call Dog Mountain.
If we can destroy it,
I firmly believe it will significantly
delay the Netherlord's plans.
Agreed.
But it's in a difficult location.
If Dog Mountain moves, we're done for.
I hate to be a vibe killer, but we already
have the Demon Lord hot on our trail.
If the big pooch piles
on, we're as good as dead.
It's true, which is why I already
sent a hunter to scout out the base.
Until he returns here with a report, I
encourage you to take this time to relax.
That said, may I borrow Boxo?
Sure, if it's okay with him. Hello there.
Then please carry him to the other room.
And Pity, could you,
Heavy, and Shui join us?
From your perspectives, what are the chances
those wayward souls will return to us?
The captain and his menagerie.
I've had the pleasure of training the
captain myself on several occasions.
Honestly, I'm a bit concerned
about having him as an enemy.
Why don't you just come out
and say it, you old coot?
As a parent yourself,
part of you finds it difficult
to blame them for their actions.
It seems our little
survey was pretty legit.
If only there was a way to
lift the curse on his son.
I'm certain he wouldn't
hesitate to turn his back.
on the Netherlord.
It's like they're trapped
in a no-win scenario.
They need Sulreem's power.
Also, you need to know, she likes the boy.
I mean, really likes him.
Time to scar him for life.
Gee, thanks for the intel.
Ix aside,
at least his life?
doesn't seem to be in danger.
The Ix is pretty thick.
I'd love to get him out of that wax sitch,
but alas, I'm merely a vending machine.
I do owe him for helping
us escape, though.
You're not the only one who
always pays his debts, Cap.
Good work with the recon.
Sir, I made it inside the base,
but there was no sign of them.
There were no boats docked either.
The place appeared to be deserted.
Thoughts, Shulami?
I can only speculate, but it's concerning.
The Netherlord may have
ordered those who escaped
by boat to rile up the
Dog Mountain Stratumlord.
That would completely wipe out all
traces of evidence as well as the base.
This stratum would be doomed.
For the time being, we'll
do more reconnaissance.
Emergency!
The Dog Mountain Stratum
Lord is on its way!
Instruct all the inhabitants to
transfer to Clearflow Lake Stratum!
It's a mighty big wave,
big enough to do us all in.
Listen up, we're evacuating.
The women and children take priority.
The tiny director can handle
getting everyone out of here.
As for us, we gotta stop
that dangerous Decay!
The way it's emerging
from the water is like
We could call it Dogzilla!
I'm not feeling confident we
can beat a whole mountain.
What did you guys do to fight back
the last time this thing attacked?
You remember Grams?
Sometimes it really seems like
Grams here is going senile on me.
We wound up in the thing's belly, then
went completely ballistic on its insides.
Hmm.
It was a close fight.
We barely won.
Whoa, so you've beaten it before?
Sure, but I was essentially
a cub when we did it,
and we only narrowly secured victory
by hacking away at its innards.
Even though I was there,
it still seems nuts to me.
We were almost doggy kibble.
You did it once, so
we'll just do it again.
That's reckless.
It's treacherous in there.
Its stomach is filled with burning
gastric acid for digestion,
so the average person would
dissolve in an instant.
Back in the day, we only dared to
challenge it after months of preparation.
He's got a point.
I vote for not burning
to death in a pup's tum.
In that case, our only
option is to get out...
We'll do it.
Pity and Voxo.
We'll attack from up
in the sky. Okay, then.
If it's useful, feel free to use the
magic items I made that can freeze water.
Are you ready?
Let's do this.
Time to fly. Hello there!
Listen, you.
Be sure to come back to me.
Yes.
You know it. Thank you.
I'll hold off on fixing that.
Judge me not, but the damage
makes me feel closer to her.
Alright, go time!
It didn't work.
Not even a little.
We'll go the Hulemy route.
Do your thing, magic items!
Wow, it's frozen.
That bought us a teensy bit of
time, but it won't last long.
Here we go!
Oh, she may like some
of the nice juicy wave.
I'll take me some of that.
We showed the big dog who the big dog is.
But now we got a scurry for our lives.
Won't be long before it
starts rampaging again.
At least we got everyone out before
this place is swallowed by waves.
Darn it.
So much for having my own stratum.
I'll miss my unelected position of power.
The directors figured out
housing for all the evacuees.
And I wanted to do my part, too.
So I decided to welcome the
newcomers with a generous flash sale.
To ease the sting of losing their
homes, they get a 90 % discount.
I'm doling out freebies to folks who
only brought the clothes on their backs.
Any vending machine worth its salt
would choose kindness over profits.
The Clear Flow Lake Stratum's kinda peak.
We already have food and
shelter pretty much on lock,
though there was a
short-lived fashion emergency.
But then we held the
Dungeon Goddess Grand Prix,
awakening everyone's inner fashionista.
This heralded the start of a
stratum-wide fashion craze.
Now everyone's Gouda on food,
clothing and shelter But what's
life without some jollies?
Speaking of,
the local men of culture
Were not so patiently
awaiting the reopening of a certain shop
Shirley recruited yours truly
to draw in new customers
Hey there, cutie
If you're feeling thirsty,
why not come inside?
Forget the sody, Bob!
I want to live!
Welcome, our new friend,
ladies. Thank you.
Keep up the great work, Boxo.
Oof.
Not even a vending machine can
resist those feminine wiles.
But I'm a one-woman appliance.
You're a real lifesaver.
I'm sure Rosie and me, the dog
fiend, is going to love these gifts.
You'd be surprised how
many people attempt to
buy the affections of
these ladies of the night.
My sage-advice and unique range
of products are hot commodities,
so I'm essentially the village wingman.
Poxo. G-Oarch?
Help me out. Hello there.
What do you know?
Even Gorth is in the mood for some lovin'.
Well, um, yeah, I was wondering if you had
thoughts on what Miss Shirley would like.
You wanna woo Miss Shirley?
Slow your roll, Icarus!
You're flying way too close to the sun!
We're talking lunatic mode with no saves,
a hopeless quest in a romantic
hell of your own making.
I really want to please her.
I know she likes cash payments.
Outside of that, I actually
don't know a whole lot about her.
I'm back. Understood.
I can check back in later.
I'm the same metal box who
helped Karyos find love.
The completionist in me would love to
couple up his partner Gorth as well.
I'm on the case.
In the name of love, I'll find out what
kind of non-dirty stuff Miss Shirley likes.
I knew I was going to need
backup, so I enlisted Lamas,
Hulemy, and Suco to help dig up the deets.
Is this really close enough to
Miss Shirley's house? Hello there.
Clue one acquired.
She works in an extravagant den of sin,
but lives in a house
that's pretty run-of-mill.
We're going to go and have a look inside.
Holler if you see someone coming.
I'd better go incognito.
It would be bad if Miss
Shirley recognized me.
Hmm?
Huh?
It's like they got their
garb from Sus R Us.
But it's fine.
Maybe they're just going
for a nice little stroll.
Well, so much for the
benefit of the doubt.
Oops. Oh, cool. You talking to me?
Well, you're the end.
I'll go scare him off!
Total overkill!
You can't disturb the peace
this early in the a .m.
Told ya!
How very odd.
I could have sworn I heard
a rabid animal screaming.
Suppose it was a bad dream.
Oh, wow.
She's just as alluring at home.
Hey, she's leaving.
Miss Shirley looks good in a dress, but
she's a real smoke show in that red vinyl.
It's like a naughty version of my outfit.
Helps that you don't have
bare skin or honkers.
I'll follow her.
She's supposed to have the whole day off.
Wonder where she's going.
I honestly can't imagine
how she spends her time.
I can't either.
My first thought was a fancy lunch at
some pricey restaurant or something.
She's not exactly dressed for that.
Where's Miss Shirley?
Hang on.
Isn't that place the local orphanage?
It sure is.
I know because Shui and I
paid them a visit recently.
Us glutton swing by sometimes
to play with the kids.
Think she came to cheer them up about
the whole not having parents thing?
Hello, hello!
Hooray! It's Miss Shirley!
Which game do you want to play?
That's a game you fall!
Will you throw it or something?
We'll play in a bit.
I need to have a word
with the director first.
After that, I'll throw
the ball or something.
Well, hot dog!
Hey, director!
Miss Shirley says she
needs to talk to you!
I know.
I could hear her very clearly.
Miss Shirley, it's always
a pleasure to see you.
It's nice to see the children so excited.
Anyway, here you go.
It's the usual amount.
I could never thank you enough
for all your generous donations.
Please, make yourself at home.
You're too kind.
Turns out, she's
literally helping orphans.
My brain's remembering something.
Shui said Miss Shirley's
also in the No Parents Club.
It turns out Miss Shirley's
kind of an incredible person.
She's a prime example of womankind.
If I were a human male, I'd
kill to take her out to dinner.
Yeah, I'd even spring for dessert.
Can't say I disagree.
Poor Gorth.
If she's the major leagues, he's
still playing t-ball in the backyard.
She's like an ancient
goddess princess angel you
can't have unless you
slay a dragon blindfolded.
I'm starting to feel like maybe it
was wrong of us to stalk her all day.
Yeah, maybe so.
Let's apologize and play with the kids
to prove we're not terrible people.
I'll play Mr.
Bear even though I'm not one.
Hey, everyone! Wow!
We're gonna run out of chairs!
Hurry!
Come play with us!
Well, look who it is.
Did you get tired of tailing me?
You saw that, huh?
I'm sorry for stalking you.
We got carried away wanting
to know more about you.
I feel awful.
We let Curiosity get the best of us.
Please don't be mad. Sorry.
You're forgiven.
But if you'd like to make amends, stick
around and spend some time with the kids.
Deal!
Mr. Bear time!
Which one of you wants
to be the bear first?
It warms the circuitry I call a
heart to see the joy on their faces.
Thank you for visiting.
You're welcome to come see us anytime.
I look forward to serving you again.
Not to keep prying, but is this
always how you spend your off days?
Guess I never really thought about it.
I don't enjoy shopping very much,
and I'm constantly bringing
delicious leftovers home from work.
Very rarely indulge in dining out. Really?
She spends her nights in a
dazzling world of excess,
but is not wasteful or indulgent herself.
She's pretty, friendly, nice
to kids, and open-minded.
Miss Shirley's in the
running for best girl!
Hello there.
Tell me, did you figure anything out?
You want me to watch something?
I won't let them get away with that.
Figured that would work.
I'll let him handle the
creepy trench coat brigade.
Seems she's even more
wonderful than I imagined.
Yes!
She'd never fall for a guy like me.
It's like a shoe loving a sock. Huh?
Quickest forfeit ever.
Guess I'll just have to be content with
watching her thrive from a distance.
I don't want to stir up trouble.
That's a surprisingly
depressing turn of events.
But that's the choice he's making.
And the customer is always right.
I've been helping Miss Shirley.
Get things rolling at her shop.
For about a week now.
But today's the last day.
Come back and see us soon.
Have a wonderful night.
I will now.
Weird.
Something's off.
Charlie!
Oh, I'm sorry.
It's just that there's something
I can't get off my mind.
If you have time, I'd
love to talk about it.
Yes, yes.
A neighbor told me there's been a lot
of suspicious activity around my house,
particularly some interesting
characters being kind of pervy.
Yup, them's the facts.
I've even had my underwear stolen
while it was hanging out to dry.
But that sort of thing
hasn't been happening lately.
And those pervy men are gone.
It's great, but strange.
So that's it.
She's in the dark about
Gorth's white knighting.
Oh, speaking of...
Hey, Boxo, did I make it in
time? Too bad! That's a shame.
I was hoping to have a
drink before heading home.
I'd love a nightcap if
you don't mind. Same.
That's the best idea I've heard in ages.
After all, I've hardly had a
drop to drink today. It's you!
I...
You're easily one of my
best customers. Really.
Chill out, my guy.
You got this.
You're the greatest.
Thanks a lot, Boxo.
Here's to a hard day's work. Right.
Cheers to that.
Poor thing.
It must be difficult to
work such late hours.
Oh, it's fine.
I mean, you know how it goes.
If I could vend love, I'd do it.
But the best I can do is late-night booze.
Still, I'll be rooting for these two.
It's a crying shame you can't
enjoy a cold beverage with us.
Honestly, I'd be thrilled to
share a midnight drink with you.
Ixnay!
I know I'm tall, dark, and well-stocked,
But now is so not the time.
Poxo.
Zoinks!
If looks could kill?
I'd be in the great factory
in the sky about now.
Bota
Mustady.
It's a story for you.
I'm waiting for you, I'm waiting for you!
I'm waiting for you, I'm feeling you!
I'm not funny, I know you are!
I know you are!
I'm not good at all, I'm not good at all.
I look forward to serving you again.